{
    "subject": "resource/Billy_Nair",
    "predicate": "ontology/birthPlace",
    "object": "resource/Durban",
    "human_readable": "Billy Nair was born in Durban.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9783633947372437,
            "question": "Is Durban the place where Billy Nair was born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8266746997833252,
            "question": "Who was born in Durban?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.810606837272644,
            "question": "Where was Billy Nair born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7063988447189331,
            "question": "What is the birthplace of Billy Nair?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6055067181587219,
            "question": "Can you tell me the birthplace of Billy Nair?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.569377064704895,
            "question": "Where did Billy Nair originate from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.565542995929718,
            "question": "Durban is known as the birthplace of whom?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5295878052711487,
            "question": "What city is associated with Billy Nair's birth?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4494510889053345,
            "question": "If someone were to ask about Billy Nair's place of birth, what would you say?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32777851819992065,
            "question": "In which city did Billy Nair come into the world?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Billy Nair was born in Durban.",
            "html": "dbpedia_8386_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=If someone were to ask about Billy Nair's place of birth, what would you say?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8386_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What city is associated with Billy Nair's birth?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8386_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Durban is known as the birthplace of whom?",
            "html": "dbpedia_8386_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8386_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8386_17.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8386_18.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8386_22.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8386_34.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8386_48.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8386_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8386_64.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8386_7.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_8386_8.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation of the triple \"Billy Nair was born in Durban\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThe documents mention that Billy Nair was born in Sydenham, Durban (multiple times), which is a part of the city of Durban. Therefore, it can be concluded that he was indeed born in Durban."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe context information provided mentions that Billy Nair was born on 27 November 1929 in Sydenham, Durban. Therefore, the statement \"Billy Nair was born in Durban\" is supported by the given documents."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Extremely Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}